ظآزLove's little quiz
takes seven parts sweetظآز
ظآزAnd three parts bitter,
till you and I meetظآز
ظآزI pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stayظآز
ظآزWaiting for youظآز
ظآزWe've got so many
romantic dreams to unfoldظآز
ظآزFinally hearing
the I love you I long to holdظآز
ظآزFalling fast
into the swirl of your eyesظآز
ظآزIt's just too tempting, so temptingظآز
ظآزNever could I have guessedظآز
ظآزMy heart's rhythmظآز
ظآزHow beautiful it is, meeting youظآز
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 10=
Wait for me a second.
I just need to finish some work.
Hold on.
Will you cook for me?
I'm hungry.
ظآزYou walked inظآز
Can you not work tonight?
Stay with me instead.
Alright.
(IP Trace Report)
What was that sound?
ظآزThe coffee's gone cold, forgot to sipظآز
ظآزJust staring at the ghost
that's stepping right upظآز
Xu Nange,
do you even know
what you're doing right now?
I...
I'm not too sure.
Why don't you teach me?
ظآزBetween us,
the two strangers staring at usظآز
You said that yourself.
ظآزOnce knew every doubt and prayersظآز
ظآزI wanna say hello, ask how you've beenظآز
ظآزTell you that these years
have curbed me inظآز
ظآزWords get stuck behind my teethظآز
ظآزLike they're afraid of what you'd seeظآز
ظآزShould I mention all the nights
I thought of youظآز
ظآزOr just pretend I'm passing throughظآز
ظآزMy heart says run,
my mouth stays stillظآز
ظآزWatching you sit there,
against my worldظآز
ظآزI walk away,
chair pulls out with a screechظآز
ظآزSay the only thing I feel cannyظآز
ظآزLong time no seeظآز
ظآزYou smile and smile,
said ظ£Yeah me tooظإظآز
ظآزThe coffee's cold, but I don't careظآز
Beiyan, the tech department
came back with a new network address.
About that...
You were right.
That Dr. X really is
the strategic partner
our group urgently needs right now.
Yeah, braised beef brisket with radish.
I think beef brisket with radish
sounds especially good.
Let's have that for dinner tonight.
Beiyan.
Y-Yeah, beef brisket sounds good.
I came to deliver the network address.
This is the confirmed final version.
(There's another report too.)
(Are you really just)
(trying to recruit
this Dr. X as a partner?)
A world-renowned medical expert
living on some deserted island
in the South Pacific?
Or even the middle
of a desert wasteland?
That's obviously fake at a glance.
(I panicked for nothing.)
(So the third firewall layer)
(was never actually breached.)
(Thank you, GitHub.)
Fake?
Nange,
I'll drive you back later.
No need.
I suddenly feel like dinner's something
I can handle by myself.
I'll head out first then.
You two carry on.
Um, she's...
Madam.
Why are you here?
Are you alright?
I...
I'm fine. Really.
Nothing's wrong.
Really? Because your face
is completely red right now.
I just put on too much blush today.
Mm-hmm. I get it.
A little romance and excitement.
Don't worry though.
I absolutely won't tell anyone.
Go do your work already.
There's really not much left to do.
Everything Mr. Huo assigned me
has already been handled perfectly.
Look.
Take the Dr. X investigation
for example.
I, Special Assistant Shen Yan,
put in major effort for that one.
You put in major effort?
Yup.
That's right.
Then I really ought
to thank you on his behalf.
You're amazing.
Did I...
offend...
Mrs. Huo somehow?
Madam.
(Geolocation: Linhai Medical University)
(This real IP trace report is in my hands now.)
(Network access point:
Campus Core Switch S-07 Port)
(IP: Linhai Medical University)
(Which means the biggest clue right now)
(is known only to me.)
(But why)
(would one of Dr. X's papers
from last year)
(show up at Linhai?)
(Could Xu Nange actually know Dr. X?)
(Beiyan,)
(it seems both you and Xu Nange)
(are hiding secrets.)
Zichen.
Beiyan.
Zichen,
something on your mind?
No.
I'm really fine. If anyone has something
on their mind, it should be you.
You're busy every single day.
I'm used to it by now.
Beiyan, you're this busy every day,
and you never talk to anyone about it?
We used to tell each other everything.
Well, you went overseas.
Just because I went overseas
doesn't mean you don't have
other friends to talk to.
We're adults now.
It's not like we all have that many emotions
we need to vent about anymore.
Beiyan,
I'm not as strong as you.
Zichen, are you still...
Don't, Beiyan.
It's all in the past.
Let's not bring it up again.
I just came back to the country,
and taking over company matters
hasn't been going very smoothly.
But I'm the second son,
the future number two.
I'm worried
I'll embarrass the Huo family.
I understand.
You feel wronged,
but you don't want to show it too much
and seem weak.
But you can try my method.
Talk to Grandma.
Grandma?
Forget whether she can comfort me,
she probably won't even understand
what I'm saying.
Actually,
sometimes having a good listener
is already enough.
Got it.
Don't stay too late.
Go back early.
Okay, Beiyan.
Grandma,
you've favored Beiyan
since we were kids.
I can understand that.
After all, he's excellent.
But now he's teaming up
with Xu Nange to fool me.
That can't still be my fault, right?
You have to judge this fairly for me.
Grandma,
this time, you have to help me.
Even if it's just this once.
(Xu Nange and Dr. X)
(must be connected somehow.)
(And Beiyan,)
(the way you're so desperate
to find Dr. X)
(is very suspicious too.)
(I have a very clear feeling)
(that Dr. X)
(is my most important breakthrough.)
(Beiyan,)
(since you don't like sharing)
(your thoughts with anyone,)
(then talk to Grandma more.)
(I'll be waiting.)
ظآزWhat destiny brought us to meetظآز
ظآزTwo different worlds, a love so sweetظآز
ظآزA wish we made
in a past life, it seemsظآز
ظآزDestined to cross time and dream ظآز
ظآزLike a fairytale story toldظآز
ظآزA gentle breeze feels so boldظآز
ظآزAs your hair brushes past your earظآز
ظآزI long to kiss your cheek, my dearظآز
ظآزAll my longing, all my love for youظآز
ظآزHas never changed, it's forever trueظآز
ظآزIt's the hand of fate
that we meet againظآز
ظآزLet me hold you once againظآز
ظآزResting against your chestظآز
ظآزYour warmth shines like stars at nightظآز
ظآزLet me kiss you once againظآز
ظآزNo reason neededظآز
ظآزMy heart belongs to youظآز
ظآزI'm not afraid
to cross time to find youظآز